Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 29 Records, 1967-1990 AIS.1995.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Service Employees International Union Local 29 Records
1967-1990
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Service Employees International Union. Local 29 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
AIS.1995.09
10 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
Service Employees International Union Local 29 represented custodial workers, housekeepers and groundskeepers in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. This collection contains employee records, grievances, and contract negotiation information regarding workers of SEIU Local 29 and their employers.
Previous Citation
Service Employees International Union Local 29 Records, 1967-1990, AIS.1995.09, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
History
Service Employees International Union Local 29 was founded in 1937 by Charles C. Levey. Local 29 represented custodial workers, housekeepers and groundskeepers in Pittsburgh, Pa. In 1999, the local merged with SEIU Local 585.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains employee records, grievances, and arbitration documentation regarding workers of SEIU Local 29 and their employers. Also included are correspondence and job announcements from individual buildings where workers were represented by the local. Information on contract negotiations and agreements are also present.
Access Restrictions
Due to the high level of personnel records scattered through this collection, researchers wishing to consult this material must sign a confidentiality agreement. This restriction will be lifted 75 years after the date of record creation. For more information please contact the Archives Service Center.
Acquisition Information
Donated in 1995.
Related Material
Rosemary Trump Papers, 1950-2005, AIS.2005.04, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Service Employees International Union, Local 585 Records, 1980-2000, AIS.1982.14, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Personnel records; Collective labor agreements; Pittsburgh (Pa.); Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Cleaning personnel -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Service industries workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor; Service Employees International Union. Local 29 (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Yoedt, John B.; Terry, Ralph E.
- Gateway Center Buildings, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- General Teamsters, Chauffeurs and Helpers Local Union 249, 1961-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Greater Pittsburgh Airport, Associated Cleaning in Commercial Area, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Grant Building, Arbitration Data, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Grant Building, Commonwealth Building Management, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Grant Building, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Graphic Arts Building, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Greater Pittsburgh Airport, Civic Center Cleaning Co., 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Greater Pittsburgh Airport, City Service, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Greater Pittsburgh Airport, Associated Cleaning in Tenant Area, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Gulf Building, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Carnegie Mellon Performance Reports, 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Carnegie Mellon University Correspondence, 1974-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
- Carnegie Mellon Vending Contract Negotiations, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Carnegie Mellon University Negotiations, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Allegheny County Housing, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Allegheny Center Mall and Buildings, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Allegheny Building, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Allegheny Center Apartments, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A.B.M. Negotiations, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- American Building Maintenance at Carnegie Mellon University, 1982-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
- Allegheny County Housing Authority, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bigelow Apartments, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bank Center Limited, 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Blue Cross Building, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Bristol Apartments, 1979-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Carlow College, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Centre City Towers, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Century Building, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Chatham College, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Civic Building, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Chamber of Commerce, 1977-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- City Service Cleaning Contractors Inc., 1979-1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- CNG Tower, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Commerce Court, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Commonwealth Building, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Commonwealth Sanitation, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Commonwealth Sanitation, Greensburg, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Commonwealth Sanitation, Washington and Fayette Counties, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cricklewood Hill Apartments, 1978-1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Custom Food Service, 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chatham College, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Duquesne University, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Duquesne University Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Duquesne University Performance Reports, 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Duquesne University Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Gateway Security, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- DAKA Food Services, 1979-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
- Empire Building, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Equibank Building, 1979-1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Expo Mart, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 100 Fifth Ave. Building, 1967-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 301 Fifth Ave. Building, 1975-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Fisher Scientific, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Frick Building, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Gateway Center, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
- Gateway Towers, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fort Duquesne Building, 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Gateway Center Buildings, 1981-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
- Maxon Towers, 1981-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Northway Mall, 1977-1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- National Steel Building, 1982-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Northway Mall Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Office Buildings Association of Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- One Oliver Plaza, First Union Legal Data, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- One Oliver Plaza, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- One Oxford Center, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh, 1977-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Heinz Hall for the Performing Arts, 1971-1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Joseph Horne Co., 1978-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Investment Building, 1978-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- I.B.M. Building, 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Imperial Garage, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Jackman Building, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Kaufmann's Department Store, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Koppers Building, 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
- Kossman Building, 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
- Liberty Center, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Manor Building, 1976-1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Mellon Bank Building, 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)